belvoireagle.com 2016-09-20

# Privacy Policy

Our Site recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to our site on the Internet (Our Site) and the importance of these concerns.

GENERAL PRIVACY ISSUES Our Site recognizes the privacy concerns of visitors to our site on the Internet (www.Our Site) and the importance of these concerns. As a general policy, no personally identifiable information, such as a visitor’s name, address, e-mail address or telephone number, is automatically collected on our website simply because the site is visited. Such information is collected only when voluntarily submitted, and Our Site uses such information only for the purpose for which it was submitted.

YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION At several places on our website, Our Site allows users to send e-mail, create web pages, subscribe to the e-mail edition of Our Site, add items to a calendar and post information through other interactive means. Our Site uses this information only for the purpose it is specifically collected or submitted. Our Site does not collect, package, sell, trade or otherwise distribute to outside parties for commercial purposes the personal information provided by users of the Our Site website. Our Site does not employ a user’s personal information submitted to this site for research, advertising, marketing or sales purposes.

COOKIES Cookies are files that our website places in the browser or system folders of the user’s computer to make the user’s time spent at the website more efficient. Cookies are not used to copy information about the user from his or her hard drive, nor do they send Our Site information that the user has not voluntarily submitted to the website. The cookie file does not contain any personal information about the user. Users should consult their browser owner’s manual for instructions on how to refuse cookies, or consult other Internet sites to learn how to stop the reception of or delete completely the cookies from their hard drives.

REQUESTS FOR ADVERTISING RATES AND INFORMATION Our Site may obtain information from a user when he or she requests information online about the opportunities for advertising in the printed or online editions of Our Site, or responds to employment opportunities at Our Site or her sister newspapers. The specific information collected becomes property of Our Site and may be used to solicit requestors.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES Our Site may establish relationships with business partners that allow visitors to Our Site site to “link” or “click through” to sites operated by these partners. In some cases, the site may be branded or co-branded with Our Site or Our Site logo; however, the site is in no way operated, maintained or edited by Our Site. Our Site is not responsible for the content or privacy policies of any third party sites that may be linked to the website of Our Site or her sister newspapers.
